生活
■
向前沖
第一季 第十四集
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影視 原創翻譯制作
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
美劇字幕下載 請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻譯：??  波比  風吹日落  萌su  往兮  重案組李sir
時間軸：Ans  校對：天朝直屬  ??
■
后期 & 特效：倉鼠sama     總監：漁夫
只是賴安
It's just Ryan.
"只是賴安"  我也是有頭有臉的
"Just Ryan"? I matter.
看  我手機里有飛人博爾特的號碼
Look, I got Usain Bolt's phone number in my phone.
當今男子短跑霸主
瞧  是不是
Check it out. Look at that.
好吧  你們是愛我的  剛那什么意思
Okay, you guys love me. What is this?
西蒙回來了
Simone's back.
她是小組里出現過的
She's the most awesome, coolest person
最棒最酷的人
that's ever been in this group.
我想知道她又有什么悲劇
Ooh, I wonder what her new tragedy is.
我希望她丟了只貓
I hope she lost a cat.
跟西蒙分享悲劇簡直爽歪歪
Sharing a tragedy with Simone would be mint.
瞧瞧你們  穿的這么正式
Look at you guys. You're all dressed up.
安妮  你還穿裙子了
Anne, are you wearing a dress?
-她喜歡我的腿  -神啊
- She likes my legs. - Oh, boy.
我戴上了耳環
I put my earring back in
還把白頭發拔了拔
and had them take out a little of the gray.
她在那會兒  這小組就像天堂
When she was in the group, this was the place to be.
大家還都意氣風發
Anyone who was anyone was here.
踏歌而舞
And we danced.
你腦子里想的肯定是54錄音室吧
I'm fairly certain you're thinking of studio 54.
80年代Disco舞曲的風向標
看  西蒙就不會像你這樣
See, that's the kind of crack Simone would never make.
她會融入其中  金
She was in it, King.
不是高高在上的評判
Not above it, commenting on it.
只是我  抱歉  我不是西蒙
Just me. Sorry, I'm not Simone.
勞倫討厭西蒙
Lauren hates Simone.
我沒有討厭西蒙
I don't hate Simone.
沒準我想的確實是54錄音室
Maybe I was thinking about studio 54.
我是在這從迪克·卡維特手里搶女人的嗎
Did I steal a woman from Dick Cavett here?
60年代的著名主持人
西蒙一講故事
Whenever Simone tells a story,
她總在旁邊小聲嘀咕
she can't help but mutter under her breath.
勞倫會說  "沒這回事  西蒙
Lauren is, like, "That event not happen, Simone.
我不信  我快吐了"
I not believe this. Gag me with spoon."
你對我的印象太離奇了
Your impression of me is uncanny.
她只是喜歡做主角
She just demands a lot of attention.
還經常夸大其詞
And is prone to exaggeration.
一個欲求不滿的騙子
Ah, so a needy liar.
這種人你們都覺得比我好
That's who you think is better than me?
-伙計們  -天吶
- Guys... - Oh, my god!
她來了  她終于來了
She's here! She's finally here!
-西蒙  -西蒙
- Simone! - Simone!
她抱了我  她第一個抱了我
She hugged me. She's hugging me first.
我實在太高興了
Oh, I'm just so happy.
好棒
Yes!
我沒看出她欲求不滿啊
I don't see the appeal.
-我看出來了  -好吧  我也看出來了
- I do. - Yeah, me too.
我在馬拉喀什的集市上
I was in the bazaar in Marrakesh
看到了這九條最絢麗的披巾
when I saw the nine most colorful scarves
就想起了我認識的最多彩的九個人
and thought of the nine most colorful people I know.
安妮  你的眼睛好幽藍
Anne, your eyes look so blue.
是因為這披巾  無可挑剔的顏色
It's the scarf. It's the perfect color.
這些披巾把我們襯得好漂亮
The scarves are making us beautiful.
是你們讓披巾美麗起來
I think you make the scarves beautiful.
你一定是賴安了
And you must be Ryan.
我不需要披巾
Oh, I don't need a scarf.
我本身就很美
I'm already beautiful.
我沒有披巾了
I don't have a scarf,
但尤蘭達用電郵給我發了你的照片
but I had Yolanda email me a picture of you.
而我一向水彩不離身
Unfortunately, I'm never without my watercolors.
我喜歡
I love it.
那么西蒙
So Simone,
想和我們分享一下會回到小組的原因嗎
would you like to share with us why you returned?
是你哥哥陷入昏迷了嗎
Is your brother in a coma?
你們也知道  我第一次加入小組
As you know, I first joined this group
是因為一次意外受傷中斷了我的事業
when my career was cut short by a tragic injury.
我不得不向我的舞蹈生涯道別
And I had to say, "farewell" to dance.
其實根本沒有證據
Although there was no evidence
證明她受過傷  或跳過舞
of an injury or a dance career.
嘀嘀咕咕  跳過舞
Blah, blah, blah, blah. Dance career.
我唯有前進  探索未來
I left in search of the next thing.
我去了歐洲  找尋美麗
I went to europe, seeking beauty.
進行藝術創作...
I was making art--
忘了我已經回到美國了
I forgot I'm back in the states.
況且現在也不是1937年
And it's not 1937,
你也不是那只企鵝
and you're not the penguin.
1937年美國百樂香煙公司在煙盒中加入企鵝形象的漫畫卡片來做宣傳
你最好也笑出聲來  不然朋友沒得做
You better laugh at that, or we're not friends anymore.
我笑得眼淚要出來了
I'm torn about this.
我在塞納河邊描繪農莊的時候
I was sketching farm houses on the Seine
遇到了一位詩人  我的心靈伴侶
when I met a poet-- my soul mate.
咱能速度快點嗎
Can we speed this up?
我還有事想和大家討論呢
I've got some things I'd like to discuss.
我從未對一個人如此動心過
I had never fallen so hard for anybody.
于是我向他求婚了
I asked him to marry me.
但婚禮那天  他消失了
And on the day we were to wed, he disappeared.
-不是吧  -天吶
- Oh, no! - Ohh...
我心碎得無法用言語表達
Words do not exist to express my heartbreak.
不  不對
No, that's not true.
有一個古蓋爾語
There is an ancient Gaelic phrase.
[痛徹心扉]
Briseadh croi.
對  就是這個
Yeah. That's it.
謝謝你  本杰明
Thank you, Benjamin.
本杰明  你居然告訴她你真名
"Benjamin"? You told her your name?
我覺得她承受得住
I felt like she could handle it.
回來的感覺真是太好了
It feels good to be here.
不說我了  賴安有事要說
But enough about me. Ryan had something.
是啊  賴安  你還能說點啥
Yeah, Ryan. Follow that.
人家可剛失去了心中摯愛
She just lost the love of her life.
我的摯愛都死了
Mine died.
都好幾個月之前了  真沒勁
Yeah, like months ago. Uck.
你們都知道  工作是我宣泄情緒的通道
Well, as you all know, work has been a refuge.
我的秀是我的一切
My show is everything to me.
你辦藝術展嗎
Oh, you're in the arts?
是電臺的體育節目
Sports radio.
全是些比分啊  胸大無腦的運動員啊
It's all scores, boobies,
還有施瓦辛格時期的落后套話
and Schwarzenegger impressions.
廣告之后是更多橄欖球訊息
More NFL after the break.
我會回來的
I'll be back.
來  繼續說吧
Yeah, go ahead.
好啊
Okay.
本來應該做我精神支柱和摯友的史蒂文
Steven, who's supposed to be my advocate and best friend,
告訴我從現在開始
informs me that, from now on,
我的節目要被砍去15分鐘
my show is gonna be 15 minutes shorter.
你們能相信嗎  砍了15分鐘
Can you believe that? 15 minutes shorter.
西蒙  你現在住哪啊
So, Simone, where are you staying?
-能跟我一起住嗎  -跟我一起住吧
- Oh, will you stay with me? - Stay with me?
跟我住
Me!
安妮  我愿意跟你一起住
Anne, I'd love to stay with you.
太棒了
Yeah!
孩子們都不在家  我把我房間讓給你
The kids are away. I'll--I'll give you my room.
我堅持這樣做
I insist.
你確定不想跟我同床共枕嗎
You sure you don't want to share a bed?
西蒙  別逗我了
Simone. Silly.
我話還沒說完呢
I'm in the middle of saying something.
有人聽我講話嗎
Is anybody listening to me?
我聽著呢
I am.
史蒂文本來是你朋友
Steven was your friend.
但他卻將你的體育節目
And then he cut your sports show
從三小時砍到兩小時45分鐘
from 3 hours to 2 hours and 45 minutes.
這是最嚴重的背叛
That is the ultimate betrayal.
你的冤情將得昭雪
And you will be avenged.
唯一聽我講話的還是這副瘋樣
And there goes the only person who listens to me.
我的錯
My bad.
抱歉用后背扎了你的劍
Sorry I hit your sword with my back.
來  丹尼  我來幫你
Here, Danny. Let me help you.
謝了
Thanks.
這些是離婚文件嗎
Hey, are these divorce papers?
你終于給那劈腿狐貍精來點厲害的了
You're finally giving that cheating harpy the boot.
我不能說我很崇拜你
I--no, I can't say that I respect you,
但你的形象沒有以前那么卡通了
but you seem less like a cartoon dog to me.
-真的嗎  -是呀
- Really? - Mm-hmm.
是啊  是該向前看了
Yeah, time to move on.
偷偷告訴你  我正暗戀小組里的某人
Between us, I'm sweet on somebody in the group.
我現在是春心萌動少年情愁啊
I am developing the darndest, most confusing feelings.
大齡男還能少年情懷總是癡  不容易
This innocent, mayberry sexuality on an old guy--mm.
丹尼  為什么這些文件
Danny, why is this paperwork
說的全是她將分到的財產啊
all about what she is gonna get?
誰是你的律師啊
Who the hell is your lawyer?
是邦妮請的  人很好
Oh, some nice guy Bonnie picked out.
你妻子請的
Your wife?
對啊  我們倆用的都是他
Yeah. We're both using him.
這樣多省事  對吧
Makes things easier, don't you think?
你好啊  索尼婭
Oh, hey, Sonia.
你知道丹尼正在辦離婚嗎
Did you know Danny is getting a divorce?
很明顯  他喜歡上了一個小組成員
Apparently, he likes someone in the group.
真的嗎
Really?
他要被凈身出戶了
Oh, he's gonna get taken to the cleaners.
你能幫幫他嗎  你辦離婚案嗎
Can you help him? Do you do divorces?
我是個訴訟律師
I'm a prosecutor.
我將罪犯綁上電椅
I put sleazebags in the chair
讓他們與世界吻別
and divorce them from existence.
你考慮考慮幫幫丹尼吧
I want you to think about helping Danny.
不過最重要的是
But more importantly,
我能去參觀執行死刑嗎
can I come to an execution?
不  你至少得先試一次
No, you gotta give it a try just once.
-你好  K佬  -下午好  卡麗
- Hi, Mr. K. - Good afternoon, Carrie.
見到你真高興
Wonderful to see you.
抽你的每一下
That is one slap
都是為了你從賴安身上奪走的七分半鐘
for every 7 and half minutes you took from Ryan.
搞什么嘛
What the hell?
史蒂文  快看你的車
Steven, look at your car.
我的愛車啊
Sweetheart.
嘿  勞倫
Oh, hey, Lauren.
-天啊  -原來你在這啊
- Oh, God. - There you are.
合十禮[印度禮儀]
Namaste.
你來這干嗎
What are you doing here?
沒聽說過私人空間這一說嗎
You've never heard of boundaries?
西蒙這么整不行啊
Simone's not working out.
她就要掌控整個小組了
She's taken over the group.
我知道你也煩心
I know it bothers you.
-我能看出你在生悶氣  -我沒有生悶氣
- I can tell you're pent up. - I'm not pent up.
你知道現在西蒙在干啥么
You know where Simone is right now?
她正和組員們在安妮的家里
She's at Anne's house with the group,
描繪彼此的美麗
so that they can paint each other's beauty.
啥
What?
她還發給我一首勵志詩
She sent me an inspirational poem.
寫得爛透了  這明明是你的招數
That stuff sucks. That's your stuff.
-你才是大爛人啊  -是啊
- You get to suck. - Yeah.
我們得把她從小組中驅除
We need to eliminate her from the group.
賴安  我要給你
Ryan, I'm gonna give you
和福斯塔在你第一次小組討論后
the same piece of advice I gave to Fausta
想要把你踢走時
when she wanted to fusilart you
我曾給她的建議
after your first session.
什么
What?
調整心態  繼續前進
Filed away. Keep going.
什么都別做
Do nothing.
相信我  相信小組
Trust me. Trust the group.
終有一天...
And in time...
賴安  你來了
Ryan, you came.
拿支畫筆  找一位你認為美麗的人
Grab a paintbrush and find someone you think is beautiful.
身邊的人就行
You won't have to look far.
-不會有用的  -什么
- It's not working out. - What?
你對小組使的那些技倆
You. The group.
自從我加入之后整個小組都高歌猛進
We've hit a nice stride since I joined.
你不適合我們
You don't fit.
你讀了我發給你的詩了嗎
Did you read the poem I sent you?
我才沒讀那首蠢詩呢
No, I didn't read the stupid poem
那個什么"呀疵"寫的
You sent me by "Yee-ahts."
我知道應該念葉慈
I realize it's pronounced Yeats,
葉慈  愛爾蘭著名詩人
我就是要故意念錯  削弱這名字的氣勢
But I'm mispronouncing it to take away its power.
你反應過激了  我們能夠和平相處的
You're overreacting. There's room for both of us.
你錯了
You are wrong.
都聽著  我有話要說
Everybody, a word.
賴安  我們發現了美
Ryan, we find beauty.
-我畫了歐文  -他是裸著的
- I draw Owen. - He's naked.
沒必要畫裸體像  真心的
Doesn't need to be. Is.
繪畫時間結束  讓她走人
Painting time's over. She's gotta go.
不不不  賴安  這可是西蒙
No, no, no. Ryan, this is Simone.
尤蘭達才是那個多余的人
Yolanda is the one who we don't want.
行了  你根本幫不上忙
Okay, that is not helping.
掀翻我朋友的車也不叫幫忙
Nor did it help when you turned my friend's car upside-down.
這是一種很不得體的行為
That is not appropriate human behavior.
好吧
Okay.
那我們來討論一下什么叫得體的行為
Can we just say what is appropriate human behavior?
干嘛小題大做  我們喜歡西蒙
Why all the drama? We like Simone.
好吧  我也不想這么做
All right. I don't want to do this.
但你們必須做出選擇
But you're gonna have to choose.
有她沒我  懂嗎
Her or me, okay?
我相信你們都會選擇我的
And I think you will all choose me.
除了現場某位豐腴的女士
Except for a certain buxom someone
我聽說她很早以前就想把我轟出去了
who I heard has already tried to have me eliminated.
他知道了
He knows.
你們到底選誰
So what's it gonna be?
她還是我
Her or me?
嗨  勞倫
Hey, Lauren.
記得我答應過你不會做的那件事嗎
Remember that thing I said I wasn't gonna do?
-我做了  還失敗了  -那是歐文嗎
- It didn't go well. - Is that Owen?
是的
Oh, yeah.
福斯塔給我的安慰獎
Fausta gave it to me as a consolation prize.
-不是很管用啊  -對  感覺更糟了
- Doesn't make it better. - No, it makes it worse.
我的客戶  你的妻子
My client, your wife,
向你索要如下財產
is asking for the following in the divorce.
房子  我的車
House, my car.
我的軍人撫恤金
My military pension.
感覺像被敲了竹杠一樣
Seems like I might be getting rooked here.
你是我的律師  你怎么說
You're my lawyer. What do you think?
我認為我們還是接受的好
I think we gotta take it.
我付給你的錢真沒白花
It's why I pay you the big bucks.
丹尼  把筆放下
Danny, put down the pen!
快滾開  你這個開保時捷
Back off, you porsche-driving,
住冷水峽谷豪宅
coldwater canyon mansion-living,
哈佛畢業的狗娘養的敗類
Harvard name-dropping mother [beep]!
他有新律師了
He has a new lawyer.
-你愿意幫我  -是的
- You're gonna help me? - Yeah.
你人好好哦
You're so sweet.
你可不能讓他這么想
Well...you can't let him think that.
這下我只能...
Now I have to--
氣勢回來了
balance restored.
歡迎收聽節目
Thanks for joining us.
今天的話題是團隊凝聚力
Our topic today is team chemistry
如何能輕易被瓦解
and how it can easily be undermined.
今天的嘉賓是泰瑞爾·歐文斯
Our guest, Terrell Owens.
泰瑞爾  你在牛仔隊時
Terrell, so when you were with the Cowboys--
我以為你請我來是為了上次
I thought you brought me here to apologize
朝我亂扔水果的事情道歉
for throwing fruit at me the last time.
好吧  很抱歉朝你亂扔水果
Right. Sorry about that fruit thing.
你在牛仔隊時
So when you were with the Cowboys,
牛仔隊可是超級碗隊伍  但是
they were a Super Bowl contender, but...
道歉太沒誠意了
That apology didn't feel genuine.
我是個人  賴安
I'm a person, Ryan.
不是你常說的
Not a robot in, like,
施瓦辛格電影里的機器人
those Schwarzenegger movies you always talk about.
好吧  我們來電話連線吧
Okay, well, we're gonna go to the phones.
這位是來自里西達的約翰
We've got John from Reseda.
賴安  我是西蒙
Ryan, it's Simone.
我覺得你對我誤會大發了
I feel your impression of me is way off base.
我懂的  西蒙
Been there, Simone.
我覺得你應該給我個機會  賴安
I think you should give me a chance, Ryan.
我周身散發的都是愛啊
I spread awesomeness.
我們得找個晚上好好聊聊
Let's go out one night.
不是談這個的時候
We are not doing this right now.
她惹到你了
Oh, she's under your skin?
聲音挺迷人的  長得怎么樣
She sounds attractive. Is she attractive?
那什么  我們要插播一條廣告
You know what? We gonna go to a commercial,
這事我們要線下解決
and we're gonna figure this out off the air.
謝謝
Thank you.
好吧  特雷爾  你可以撤了
All right, Terrell. We're done.
你一個人搞不定的
You need help.
這他媽是...
What the--
你居然畫我  伙計
Did you paint a picture of me, man?
你好
Hi.
你離我遠點
You stay away from me.
-你知道我的  -不  我不知道
- Look, you know me. - No, I don't know.
你知道要我說出我"次臥了"是很難的
And you know I have a hard time saying I'm-- w-rong.
讓我接受指責很簡單
It's easy for me to accept blame.
但我對于不發音的"W"有著認知問題
I just have a cognitive problem with my silent "W"s.
奇怪的是
It's weird,
"洗爺下"它們倒是一點問題沒有
I don't have any trouble w-riting them.
我要改過自新
I need to make amends.
我給你帶了這只稀有的非洲灰鸚鵡
I have brought you this rare African grey parrot.
這是只鴿子
That's a pigeon.
我不想要你的鳥
I don't want your bird.
但我得糾正錯誤
But I have to make things right.
我給了你一巴掌  還掀翻了你的車
I slapped you, I flipped your car,
我還在你女朋友的
I poured super glue all over
電腦鍵盤上倒了一堆萬能膠
your girlfriend's computer keyboard.
女朋友
Girlfriend?
-這是誰干的  -行了
- Who did this? - Stop.
K佬  我壓根沒生你的氣
Mr. K, I'm not even mad at you.
事實上  我氣的是賴安
I'm actually mad at Ryan.
我都為他做牛做馬了
I kill myself for the guy,
他居然還背著我埋汰我
and he complains about me behind my back.
他不知道我承受的壓力有多大
He doesn't understand the pressure I face
廣告銷售  聽眾流失等等
from ad sales, from audience erosion--
不說了  算了
You know, forget it.
我不想用電臺業的細枝末節煩你
I don't want to bore you with the minutia of the radio business.
別別別
No, no, no.
我就喜歡細枝末節  都跟我說說
I love minutia. Explain it all to me.
-你說真的  -要記筆記嗎
- Seriously? - May I take notes?
不用  你沒必要做這個
No. You don't have to do that.
卡麗  把這記下來
Carrie, take this down.
丹尼  我讓你寫張你想要東西的清單
Danny, I asked you to make a list of everything you wanted,
-這就是你的清單  -是的
- and this is what you've come up with? - Yeah.
折疊沙發  手推車  歷史頻道
The pullout sofa, the wheelbarrow, the history channel.
只要歷史頻道嗎
Just the history channel?
抱歉
Sorry.
剛和約翰·利特高打完電話
I just got off the phone with John Lithgow.
美國演員、制片人、編劇
哈佛大學67屆的
Harvard '67.
那么...
So...
準備好簽字同意我客戶的要求了嗎
Ready to sign off on my client's demands?
事情將會這樣解決
This is what's gonna happen.
我的客戶不會支付贍養費
My client will pay no alimony,
他會保留自己的撫恤金
he'll retain his pension
以及一半的共同財產
and acquire half of the joint assets.
如果你想這么上法庭
If you want to take this before a judge,
我會把你當午飯吃了
I will you eat you for lunch.
你又不是離婚律師
You're not a divorce attorney.
這是我的專長
This is my specialty.
是嗎
Oh, yeah?
我的專長是贏
Well, my specialty is winning.
我會施展出我的全部能力
And I can and will do everything in my power
讓陪審團站在我這邊
to get that jury on my side.
我能讓他們
Yeah, I can rile them up
因曾經的不公而激憤得跳腳
over the injustice that's been done.
或者讓他們開懷大笑
Or I can make 'em laugh.
我也能讓他們哭
Or I can make 'em cry
因為對這個有著1/64
over the betrayal
印第安奇努克血統的人的背叛
of a 1/64th Chinook Indian.
我們竊取了他族人的土地
We stole his people's land.
而她竊取了他的家庭...
She stole his family...
他的尊嚴...
his dignity...
他的心
his heart.
讓你的客戶趕緊簽字
Have your client sign these papers now,
不然這些都會真實上演
or I do this for real.
打電話給約翰·利特高
Call John Lithgow.
告訴他你是個敗類
Tell him you're [beep] .
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
西蒙帶我上這來會有什么驚喜
What awesomeness can Simone bring me here?
等著瞧吧
Just you wait.
請再來兩杯酒  沙琳
Another round of drinks, please, Charlene.
老一套的胸牌花招
Ah, yes, the old clocking of the name tag trick.
我媽也這么干  其實沒人想被這么對待
My mom does that. Nobody wants it.
如果我們和沙琳的聯系
What if our connection to Charlene
會改變我們的生活呢
could change our lives?
沒有什么陌生人
There are no strangers...
只有我們還未相遇的朋友
only friends we haven't met yet.
我呸
Um...Yuck.
讓我們深入了解一下  真心話還是大冒險
Let's deepen our connection. Truth or dare?
你知道我們不是14歲吧
You realize we're not 14 years old, right?
-真心話大冒險  傻子  -好吧  真心話
- Truth or dare, dummy. - Fine, truth.
你和你妻子在哪遇見的
Where'd you meet your wife?
我的第一個廣播站工作
My first radio job.
她是電臺經理的女兒
She was the daughter of the station manager,
他討厭我  我就約詹妮出去
and he hated me, and I asked Janie out.
我想她只是為了氣他  所以她同意了
And, I think just to spite him, she said "Yes."
我覺得這是她跟我結婚的原因
I think that's why she married me.
以及我有六塊腹肌
That and the fact that I have a six-pack.
但是為了能讓人看見  我得把身體里的
But in order to see it, I have to breathe
空氣全都呼出去
all the air out of my body,
然后再用力地咳嗽
and then cough, like, really hard.
-真心話大冒險  -大冒險
- Truth or dare? - Dare.
好吧  你知道沙琳的名字
Okay. You know Charlene's name.
現在去要她的電話
Now get her phone number.
賴安  這是第一次
Wow, Ryan, that's the first dare
我聽到的大冒險不涉及到讓我脫衣服
I've ever heard that doesn't invol meve taking my clothes off.
說實在的
Well, in fairness to me,
我沒意識到那也是個選擇
I didn't realize that was an option.
沙琳  我們在一起很開心
Charlene, we've had a great time,
我不想就這么結束
and I don't want it to end.
告訴我你的電話號碼好嗎
Why don't you give me your number?
你不會遺憾的  我很會愛撫
You won't be sorry. I know how to do stuff.
我也很會愛撫  沙琳
I know how to do stuff too, Charlene.
很好  做得不錯
All right, that was good. Nicely done.
你選大冒險我并不驚訝
Not surprised you picked "dare" though.
你看起來就不想愛說真心話的
You don't seem to be that big a fan of truth.
好的  想要個免費的真心話嗎
Fine, you want a free truth?
好啊  那就談談你的未婚夫吧
Okay. Let's talk about your fiance.
你的今生摯愛
The love of your life.
他生日是什么時候  他最喜歡什么顏色
When's his birthday? What's his favorite color?
門基樂隊沒有被選入搖滾名人堂
Is he outraged that The Monkees
他有沒有很生氣
are not in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?
這些事我都不知道
I don't know any of those things.
我才認識他24小時
I only knew him for 24 hours.
悲劇了你
Aha! Tepid tragedy.
那就意味著他不是我今生摯愛嗎
Does that mean that he wasn't the love of my life?
你花了多長時間愛上
How long did it take for you
你的今生摯愛的
to fall for the love of your life?
不太長
Not long.
暴風雨要來了
There's a storm coming.
我跳舞的腿總是能感覺到
I can always feel it in my dance leg.
真的嗎  你在洛杉磯是預測暴風雨的
Really? You calling your shot with a storm in L.A.?
腿不會騙人
Leg never lies.
女士  你要么是我遇見過的最有趣人
Lady, you are either the most interesting person
要么就是一個病態撒謊精
I've ever met or a pathological liar.
我選真心話
I'll take truth.
你因為什么而受不了我
What about me makes you so crazy?
-你真想知道嗎  -是的
- You really want to know? - Mm-hmm.
我在這世上最親近的人
Okay, the person that I was
已經死了
closest to in the world died.
我想表現得很淡定
And I try to keep it all cool and together,
但是大多數的早晨
but most mornings, it's a miracle
我能下床都是奇跡了
I can even get out of bed.
救助小組真的幫了很大的忙
And that group really helps me.
我不知道方式  也不知道原因
I don't know how. I don't know why.
但是我不想讓你來搗亂
But I don't want you messing with that.
跟我來
Come with me.
可見效果加上投資回報率
The viewable impressions plus the ROI should equal
應該等于廣告效果
advertising effectiveness.
但是在這個不斷進步的世界中
But in a world of time-shifted content,
舊有的規則已經不適用了
the older rules no longer apply.
你在和歷史的挑戰相"布窩"斗
You are w-restling with historic challenges.
你懂的
You get it!
你是第一個愿意花時間去理解的人
You're the first person that's ever taken the time to understand.
謝了  兄弟
Thanks, buddy.
我們是兄弟了
Are we buddies?
-我能叫你兄弟嗎  -當然了
- Can I call you buddy? - Yeah, sure.
哦  兄弟
Oh, buddy.
這是我人生最輝煌的時刻了  兄弟
This is the best moment of my life, buddy.
現在去干什么
Huh? What now?
去整蠱一對關系沒有咱們好的兄弟嗎
Should we go pull a prank on some lesser pair of buddies?
我想要教訓一下賴安
I would like to teach Ryan
因為他不把我當回事
a lesson about taking me for granted.
你們是在說要教訓賴安嗎
Are we talking about teaching ryan a lesson?
-是的  -我入伙
- Yeah. - I'm in.
安妮是個奇跡創造者
Anne is a miracle worker.
我基本上得到了一切
I basically get everything.
所以你恢復單身了  太激動人心了
So you're gonna be single. That's exciting.
或許你可以當我的副手
Maybe you could be my wingman.
讓我確認一下
Let me check something.
應該沒多大競爭力
You wouldn't be too much competition.
我只要簽個名就好了
All I have to do is sign here, and it is official.
放下筆  丹尼  我們還能要更多
Put down that pen, Danny. We're gonna get more.
更多
More?
你買給她的珠寶
The jewelry that you gave her,
她爺爺奶奶的儲蓄債券
those savings bonds from her grandparents.
還有她用你的醫保治療的橫隔膜
The diaphragm that she got using your health coverage.
我不想要她的橫隔膜
I don't want a diaphragm.
賣了它  換一頂圓頂小帽
Well, sell it. Use it for a yarmulke.
就要到手了
We're getting it.
你不想因她的所做所為而報復她嗎
Don't you want her to suffer for what she did to you?
不  我希望自己能向前看
No, I just want to move on.
丹尼  那女人曾宣誓過
Danny, the woman made a vow.
她曾承諾  不管貧困富裕
She promised to be there through good times and bad,
都會永遠在你身邊
by your side, forever.
她不會因為日子趨于平淡而離開你
She doesn't get to leave because she gets bored,
也不會因結識新歡拋棄你
or she finds someone new,
亦或是忘記吃那該死的心臟病藥
or she forgets to take her damn heart medication!
你知道的  安妮
You know, Anne,
看起來你一開始的話題是一個女人
it seems like you could start talking about one woman,
-但最后卻變成了...  -我們都知道的
- but end up talking about-- - Yeah, we're already there.
感覺就像嗨了
This all feels very the wire.
-我們得到了嗎  -沒有
- Are we about to get "got"? - We don't get got.
我帶你去聚會  你或者我能艷遇
I take you to a meet so you get got or I get got,
但我們不能同時有艷遇  規矩就是這樣
but we don't both get got, 'cause it's not how it works.
是啊  我不怎么看那節目
Yeah, I don't actually watch the show.
我知道我本該如此
I know I'm supposed to.
你問我為什么帶你來這里
You asked me why I took you here.
如果你不是這么個人的話  我送你的詩
I sent you a poem that would be perfect for this
正好契合這個場景
if you weren't such a dude.
這世上充滿神奇的事物
The world is full of magical things,
耐心等待著我們用智慧...
patiently waiting for our senses...
去挖掘
to grow sharper.
-你果然讀了  -是的
- You did read it. - Yeah.
我告訴過你的
I told you.
還認為我在耍你玩嗎
Still think I'm full of it?
我不確定我是否還在意
I'm not certain I care.
很顯然
And it's pretty clear
你對帕蒂依舊充滿怨恨
you still have a lot of anger towards Patty.
那當然
Of course I do.
如果她真的愛我
If she really loved me,
她就會照顧好自己
she would have taken care of herself.
你不該給她太大壓力
You ought to cut her some slack.
我有六個心愛的孫子孫女
I got six grandchildren I love.
但我還是做著對自己沒啥好處的事
But I still do things that are bad for me.
要是有人給我搭線  我也挺愿意販毒的
Hell, I'd drop "E" if somebody would hook me up.
那是不可能的  喬治
It's not happening, George.
我都不敢睡在我們床上
I can't even sleep in our bed
那會讓我想起從前每晚我都會問
because it reminds me how every night I would say,
"你吃藥了嗎"
"Did you take your pill?"
她會親我  當著我的面撒謊
She would kiss me, lie to my face,
"吃了"
and say, "Yes."
你得學會舒緩情緒
You have to let that anger go.
你知道為什么我不恨邦妮了嗎
You know what allows me not to hate Bonnie?
因為你在基本訓練時
Blunt force trauma to your prefrontal cortex
前額皮質受到了創傷嗎
suffered during basic training?
不  那只留下了空間辨識問題
No. That just left me with a few minor spatial issues.
而邦妮  當她做的錯事
With Bonnie, when something she's done wrong
闖入我的腦袋時
pops into my head,
我會立即回憶起我們從前的開心時刻
I immediately think of all the good times we had together.
你覺得晚上
Do you think you can try sleeping
能試著睡回自己床上嗎
in your own bed tonight?
我不知道自己準備好沒
I don't know if I'm ready.
這里  就在這里
Here. It's right here.
你們說過會一直陪著我
You know, you said you would be here for me.
我不知道是字面上的意思
I didn't think you were being literal.
這個小組的人不太會暗喻
This group does not do well with metaphors.
再說了  我們做了"第一晚回床"蛋糕
Plus, we made you a first-night-in-your-bed cake.
福斯塔  這蛋糕美味極了
This cake is delicious, Fausta.
我的秘訣是
My secret:
我多加了一杯黃糖
I use an extra cup of brown sugar
還有母乳
and breast milk.
好吧  我告訴你們
Okay, you know what?
我改變注意了
I've changed my mind.
今晚我做不到
I don't think I can do this tonight.
等等  你可以的  安妮
Wait. You can do it, Anne.
回憶一下歡樂時光
Think about the good times.
你是對的
You're right.
謝謝你們
Thank you, guys.
我做得到  真的
I can do it, I can-- aah!
不  異性戀
Oh, no! Straight sex!
這是我邁出的很大一步
This is a very big step for me.
為什么在這里
Why here?
我們那時在這里道別
We were saying good night.
然后順理成章了
One thing led to another.
伙計們
Guys.
拜托了
Please.
讓我們聊一下真實感受
Let's talk about how we're all feeling.
我們聽著呢
We're listening.
很高興能和你共度一晚
I'm glad I could experience this night with you.
還有組內的一些人
And several members of the group.
我可不太受得了福斯塔那句
I could have done without Fausta saying,
"下一個我上"
"I got next."
她說的是你還是我
Did she mean me or you?
我  你都有安妮了
Me. You get Anne.
福斯塔是我的
Fausta's mine.
晚安
Good night.